const dayOneQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What are the types of Tawheed?",
    options: [
      "Ar Rububiyyah, al Uluhiyyah and al  Asmau Wasifat",
      "Al Ilah, Ar Rabb and Al Asmah",
      "As sidiq, An Nutq  and Al’amal",
      "Allah, Ar Rasul and Al Malak",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is Allah?",
    options: [
      "Everywhere",
      "In the heaven",
      "In the Mosque",
      "In  Makkah",
      "In the heart of human",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The first compulsory act on man is……………………………….",
    options: [
      "As  Salat",
      "As Shahadatayn",
      "At Taharah",
      "Az Zakah",
      "Al Hajj",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Iman (Faith) comprises of three parts, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Confirmation by  heart of all essentials of Iman, Verbal confirmation and Confirmation by  physical actions",
      "Shahadatyn, Articles of faith and Pillars of Islam",
      "Islam, At taharah and As Salat",
      "Angels, Divine revelations and Destiny",
      "Islam, Iman and Ihsan",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What are articles of faith?",
    options: [
      "To believe in Allah, His creatures, His divine  books, His messengers, the day of judgement and the destiny",
      "To believe  in Allah, His angels, His divine books, His messengers, the day of  judgement and the unknown",
      "To believe in Prophets, Angels, Divine  books, Messengers, the day of judgement and the destiny",
      "To believe in  Allah, His angels, Al Quran, His messengers, the day of death and the  destiny",
      "To believe in Allah, His angels, His divine books, His messengers, the day of judgement and the destiny",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first creature?",
    options: [
      "Al Kursiy",
      "Al ‘Arash",
      "Al Qalam",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Adam",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many walk able distances, in years, are in between each heaven to  another?",
    options: [
      "1000 years",
      "5000 years",
      "100 years",
      "500 years",
      "10  years",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Iblis was …….?",
    options: ["human being", "an angel", "a messenger", "a jinn", "a prophet"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What did Allaah created you for?",
    options: [
      "Al Jannah",
      "To worship Him",
      "Punishment",
      "Education",
      "Purification",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "On how many pillars does this religion stand on?",
    options: ["6 pillars", "7 pillars", "3 pillars", "1 pillar", "5 pillars"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Allah’s right on His slaves?",
    options: [
      "He will punish not those who do  not associate thing to him",
      "To worship Him and not associate partner to  Him",
      "To worship him",
      "To praise him",
      "To associate no partner to  Him",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Angel was assigned to blow the trumpet?",
    options: [
      "Angel Israfil",
      "Angel Mikail",
      "Angel Jibril",
      "Angel ‘Atid",
      "Angel Malik",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Allah created the soil on which day?",
    options: [
      "Yaomul Jumu’at",
      "Yaomul Ahad",
      "Yaomus Sabt",
      "Yaomul thulathai",
      "Yaomul ithnayn",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Angels were created from light while Jins were created  from…………………………..",
    options: ["Light", "Dark", "Dust", "Black", "Flame of fire"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "There are four Rivers flowing from Paradise, what are their names?",
    options: [
      "Sayhan, Jayhan, Rayhan and Bayhan",
      "Niil, Jahyan, Dayhan and Furat",
      "Furat, Niil, Sayhan and Jayhan",
      "Niil, Tasnin, Sayhan and Furat",
      "Niil, Sayhan, Jayhan and Rayhan",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
];

export default dayOneQuestions;
